Jammy and B.
Oh, can you both stand up?
Don't be shy
.  Where is your assistant?
They have a special website called
The Knowled
Base where they've uploaded 5000 videos,
and they have another 5000 videos they
're editing, so that's a total of
10,000 videos, and it's free, and it's really
hard to... uh...
do the descriptions.  Both of them
work at Dream Delivery and she's basically
completed five or six courses.  And
she reconnects with the
original language, and they, and she, do all
that work.
She and her assistant have been doing
all that work for the
past 14 years, during those dream-making courses
.  So let's give
them a round of applause!   They always
give me the
same answer when we go out for
dinner, about once a year,
and I ask if they
need money, and they
always say no. They're the
only ones who say
no; they say they don't need it, they're fine,
but they accept donations
on the website.  And I
encourage you to contribute in some way
to
that website.  They were the only people who did
n't seem to ask me for money.  Therefore,
you should help them.
D